new_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, "
                                                         "&quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was "
                                                         "all done with physical objects.",
                                             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
                                             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "The word &quot;Inception&quot; came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.",
                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
                                             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
                                             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}
